export const ufcQuiz = [
  {
    question: "Who was the first UFC Lightweight Champion?",
      option1: "Jens Pulver",
      option2: "BJ Penn",
      option3: "Frankie Edgar",
      option4: "Sean Sherk",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who is known as 'The Notorious'?",
      option1: "Nate Diaz",
      option2: "Conor McGregor",
      option3: "Khabib Nurmagomedov",
      option4: "Michael Chandler",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who defeated Ronda Rousey to end her undefeated streak?",
      option1: "Holly Holm",
      option2: "Amanda Nunes",
      option3: "Miesha Tate",
      option4: "Cris Cyborg",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter retired undefeated with a 29-0 record?",
      option1: "Georges St-Pierre",
      option2: "Khabib Nurmagomedov",
      option3: "Jon Jones",
      option4: "Anderson Silva",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first double champ (holding two UFC belts simultaneously)?",
      option1: "Conor McGregor",
      option2: "Daniel Cormier",
      option3: "Henry Cejudo",
      option4: "Amanda Nunes",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the most title defenses in UFC history?",
      option1: "Kamaru Usman",
      option2: "Georges St-Pierre",
      option3: "Anderson Silva",
      option4: "Demetrious Johnson",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Who knocked out Jose Aldo in 13 seconds?",
      option1: "Conor McGregor",
      option2: "Max Holloway",
      option3: "Chad Mendes",
      option4: "Alexander Volkanovski",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter is known as 'Bones'?",
      option1: "Jon Jones",
      option2: "Anderson Silva",
      option3: "Israel Adesanya",
      option4: "Daniel Cormier",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who defeated Anderson Silva to end his long title reign?",
      option1: "Michael Bisping",
      option2: "Chris Weidman",
      option3: "Vitor Belfort",
      option4: "Luke Rockhold",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter is nicknamed 'Blessed'?",
      option1: "Brian Ortega",
      option2: "Max Holloway",
      option3: "Charles Oliveira",
      option4: "Dustin Poirier",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the youngest UFC Champion in history?",
      option1: "Jon Jones",
      option2: "BJ Penn",
      option3: "Vitor Belfort",
      option4: "Jose Aldo",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter is known as 'The Last Stylebender'?",
      option1: "Israel Adesanya",
      option2: "Anderson Silva",
      option3: "Francis Ngannou",
      option4: "Yoel Romero",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first Mexican-born UFC Champion?",
      option1: "Cain Velasquez",
      option2: "Yair Rodriguez",
      option3: "Brandon Moreno",
      option4: "Tony Ferguson",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who is nicknamed 'Ruthless'?",
      option1: "Robbie Lawler",
      option2: "Colby Covington",
      option3: "Matt Hughes",
      option4: "Donald Cerrone",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the first ever UFC event in 1993?",
      option1: "Ken Shamrock",
      option2: "Royce Gracie",
      option3: "Dan Severn",
      option4: "Tank Abbott",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter is called 'The Eagle'?",
      option1: "Khabib Nurmagomedov",
      option2: "Islam Makhachev",
      option3: "Zabit Magomedsharipov",
      option4: "Fedor Emelianenko",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who did Daniel Cormier defeat to win the Heavyweight title?",
      option1: "Cain Velasquez",
      option2: "Stipe Miocic",
      option3: "Francis Ngannou",
      option4: "Junior dos Santos",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the fastest knockout in UFC history?",
      option1: "Jorge Masvidal",
      option2: "Conor McGregor",
      option3: "Francis Ngannou",
      option4: "Ronda Rousey",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who did Leon Edwards knock out with a head kick to win the UFC Welterweight title?",
      option1: "Kamaru Usman",
      option2: "Colby Covington",
      option3: "Tyron Woodley",
      option4: "Gilbert Burns",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which fighter is nicknamed 'Cowboy'?",
      option1: "Donald Cerrone",
      option2: "Justin Gaethje",
      option3: "Tony Ferguson",
      option4: "Clay Guida",
    answer: 1
  }
];
